♪They say time will reveal a person's heart♪
♪ يقولون الوقت سيكشف قلب الإنسان
♪In all lives, may the sea calm the tides♪
في كل حيوات البحر يهدئ المد والجزر
♪Blue silk drifting to one's hometown, carrying greed, hatred, and ignorance♪
حرير أزرق ينجرف إلى مسقط رأس المرء حاملاً الجشع والكراهية والجهل ♪
♪Going to the corners of the heavens to seek a long-awaited reunion♪
الذهاب إلى أركان السماء بحثًا عن لم الشمل الذي طال انتظاره ♪
♪To live or die together, that is but an act♪
أن نعيش معًا أو نموت معًا ، فهذا ليس سوى فعل
♪Letting down our memories♪
تخلي ذكرياتنا ♪
♪Why should we rip out our heart for a heartless person?♪
♪ لماذا يجب أن نقطع قلوبنا من أجل إنسان بلا قلب؟
♪Treating each other with courtesy is but a scene in my dream♪
معاملة بعضنا البعض بلطف ليس سوى مشهد في حلمي
♪We'll wake up eventually♪
♪ سنستيقظ في النهاية ♪
♪As the autumn wind blows, the maple leaves fall, pulling myself away♪
♪ مع هبوب رياح الخريف ، تتساقط أوراق القيقب ، وتسحب نفسي بعيدًا ♪
=Don't Forget My Love= =Episode 21=
= لا تنسى حبي = = الحلقة 21 =
The crown prince...
ولي العهد ...
The crown prince has arrived.
وصل ولي العهد.
Could it be
هل من الممكن ذلك
that he changed his mind?
أنه غير رأيه؟
(Seems like I was mistaken.)
(يبدو أنني كنت مخطئا).
Take another sip.
خذ رشفة أخرى.
Are you awake?
هل انت مستيقظ؟
Qianyu.
Qianyu.
Do you feel better?
هل تشعر بتحسن؟
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
That's great.
ذلك رائع.
Let me see.
دعني أرى.
I feel much better.
أشعر أفضل بكثير.
The black line is gone!
ذهب الخط الأسود!
You're fine now.
أنت بخير الآن.
I knew that physician was a quack doctor.
كنت أعرف أن الطبيب كان طبيبًا دجالًا.
I'll bring you something nice.
سأقدم لك شيئًا لطيفًا.
Wait here.
انتظر هنا.
Okay.
تمام.
(If only this moment could last forever.)
(إذا كانت هذه اللحظة فقط يمكن أن تستمر إلى الأبد).
Ah!
آه!
Qianyu?
Qianyu؟
Who are you?
من أنت؟
Why did you capture me?
لماذا قبضت علي؟
My daughter,
ابنتي،
it's your father.
انه والدك.
Huh?
هاه؟
Father, is that really you?
أبي ، هل هذا حقا أنت؟
You're still alive?
انت لازلت حيا؟
Silly girl,
فتاة سخيفة،
I'm not dead.
انا لست ميت.
I'm doing fine.
أنا بخير.
Father, I missed you!
أبي اشتقت لك!
My daughter,
ابنتي،
I missed you too.
اشتقت إليك أيضا.
That's why
لهذا
I have no choice but to bring you here in advance.
ليس لدي خيار سوى إحضاركم إلى هنا مقدمًا.
Father, what's going on here?
أبي ، ما الذي يحدث هنا؟
The entire Prime Minister Yun's Residence was wiped out.
تم القضاء على مقر إقامة رئيس الوزراء يون بأكمله.
I...
أنا...
I saw you when you were...
رأيتك عندما كنت ...
But now, you are...
لكن الآن ، أنت ...
And Yan Chi.
ويان تشي.
Where did you send him?
إلى أين أرسلته؟
He has his mission to complete.
لديه مهمته لإكمال.
From this moment onward,
من هذه اللحظة فصاعدا ،
do not ask any questions.
لا تسأل أي أسئلة.
Just stay here like the good girl you are.
فقط ابقي هنا مثل الفتاة الطيبة أنت.
If so...
لو ذلك...
If so, tell me about
إذا كان الأمر كذلك ، أخبرني عنها
the truth behind the massacre.
الحقيقة وراء المجزرة.
The body looked just like you.
بدا الجسد مثلك تمامًا.
Was it just an illusion?
هل كان مجرد وهم؟
And Yan Chi,
ويان تشي
he kept telling me to acquire the Tiger Tally that can command the three armies.
ظل يخبرني بالحصول على Tiger Tally الذي يمكنه قيادة الجيوش الثلاثة.
Could it be
هل من الممكن ذلك
that it was all part of your plan?
أن كل هذا كان جزءًا من خطتك؟
I didn't expect you
لم أكن أتوقعك
to become this scheming and overbearing
ليصبح هذا مكيدة ومتعجرف
after spending some time with Jun Lingchuan.
بعد قضاء بعض الوقت مع Jun Lingchuan.
Father,
أب،
just tell me the reason.
فقط قل لي السبب.
What are you guys up to?
ماذا تودون أن تفعلوا؟
Fine.
بخير.
Since you want to know it that badly,
بما أنك تريد أن تعرف ذلك بشكل سيء ،
I guess I can enlighten you.
أعتقد أنه يمكنني تنويرك.
♪My longing knows no bounds, in memories I wallow♪
شوقي لا يعرف حدودا ، في الذكريات أغمق ♪
♪Us and our wishful thinking♪
♪ لنا وتفكيرنا بالتمني ♪
♪When memories turn into poetry♪
عندما تتحول الذكريات إلى شعر ♪
♪Which poem will be yours?♪
♪ أي قصيدة ستكون لك؟ ♪
♪Year after year, an instant change♪
♪ سنة بعد سنة ، تغيير فوري
♪The few nights that contain our memories♪
الليالي القليلة التي تحتوي على ذكرياتنا ♪
♪Looking as the stars vanish, you grew distant from me♪
♪ بالنظر إلى اختفاء النجوم ، ابتعدت عني
♪Why can't I forget about you?♪
♪ لماذا لا أنساك؟
♪Words after words, tears flowing down♪
♪ كلمات تلو الكلمات ، الدموع تتدفق ♪
♪As the trees and plants wither♪
كما تذبل الأشجار والنباتات
♪Where are you during New Year's Eve?♪
♪ أين أنت في ليلة رأس السنة؟
♪Can you please look back?♪
♪ هل يمكنك الرجوع للوراء من فضلك؟
♪Just once♪
♪ مرة واحدة فقط ♪